Petra
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Petra
2.1.1.1.22
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1236
- Petra, 2.1.1.1.22
  - Bedouins, road from Petra, 1908; 49; 2042; 540; 4x5 (Box 1236)
  - Bedouin tents and woman, 1908; 50; 2043; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Bedouin tents, road from Petra, 1908; 51; 2044; 541; 4x5 (Box 1236)
  - Bedouins at Bustah (copy), 1908; 52; 2045; 4x5 (Box 1236)
  - Bedouin tents, return trip from Petra, 1908; 53; 2046; 720; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Bedouins at Bustah, 1908; 54; 2047; 731; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Bedouin tents at Bustah, 1908; 55; 2048; 732; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Bedouin boys, 1908; 56; 2049; 742; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Bedouins in desert, 1908; 57; 2049A; 4x5 (Box 1236)
  - Bedouin children at Bustah, 1908; 58; 2050; 746; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Bedouin children at Bustah (copy), 1908; 59; 2050A; 5x7 (Box 1236)
  - Water skin in front of Bedouin tents, 1908; 60; 2051; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Bedouin tent at Bustah, road from Petra, 1908; 61; 2052; 552; 4x5 (Box 1236)
  - Bedouin tents, 1908; 62; 5x7 film (Box 1236)
  - The camp, 1908; 63; 2053; 648; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Cooking tent, 1908; 64; 2054; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - H. Troth’s tent, 1908; 65; 2055; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Unfinished temple, 1908; 66; 2056; 747; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Temple of the Urn, 1908; 67; 2057; 659; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - The Deir, 1908; 68; 2058; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Entrance to Petra, 1908; 69; 2059; 654; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Looking from theater, 1908; 70; 2060; 647; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Single oleanders at Petra, 1908; 71; 2061; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Altar of sacrifice, 1908; 72; 2062; 572; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Row of tombs on high ground above the Deir, 1908; 73; 2063; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Obelisks on high place, 1908; 74; 2064; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Obelisks on high place, 1908; 75; 2064A; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Gorge leading to high place, 1908; 76; 2065; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Tombs on heights above the Deir, 1908; 77; 2066; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Tomb on height above the Deir, 1908; 78; 2067; 565; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Old temple ruins, 1908; 79; 2068; 560; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - View showing rock formation, 1908; 80; 2069; 558; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - View from high place, 1908; 81; 2070; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Stairway in rocks near camp, 1908; 82; 2071; 4x5 (Box 1236)
  - Group in coffee room on road to Petra, 1908; 83; 2349; 690; 5x7 (Box 1236)
  - Group in coffee room on road to Petra, 1908; 84; 2349A; 5x7 (Box 1236)
  - Frank R. Roberson at Aaron’s Tomb on Mount Hor, 1908; 85; 2353; 706; 5x7 (Box 1236)
  - Frank R. Roberson at Aaron’s Tomb on Mount Hor, 1908; 86; 2353A; 5x7 (Box 1236)
  Box 1237
- Petra, 2.1.1.1.22
  - Mount Hor and Aaron’s Tomb, 1908; 1; 2354; 19; 5x7 (Box 1237)
  - Place of sacrifice, 1908; 2; 2355; 20; 5x7 (Box 1237)
  - Pool of blood on high altar, 1908; 3; 2356; 695; 5x7 (Box 1237)
  - West Wall from place of sacrifice, 1908; 4; 2357; 688; 5x7 (Box 1237)
  - Rock showing altar of sacrifice, 1908; 5; 2359; 721; 5x7 (Box 1237)
  - Amphitheater, 1908; 6; 2360; 711; 5x7 (Box 1237)
  - Columbarium, 1908; 7; 2361; 718; 5x7 (Box 1237)
  - Tomb of the lions, 1908; 8; 2362; 587; 5x7 (Box 1237)
  - Tombs of the Governor, 1908; 9; 2363; 722; 5x7 (Box 1237)
  - Deir, 1908; 10; 2364; 725; 5x7 (Box 1237)
  - General view of the Eastern Wall, 1908; 11; 2365; 717; 5x7 (Box 1237)
  - Eastern Wall, 1908; 12; 2366; 25; 5x7 (Box 1237)
  - Temple in East Wall with Corinthian pillars, 1908; 13; 2367; 701; 5x7 (Box 1237)
  - Dwelling at beginning of East Wall, 1908; 14; 2368; 715; 5x7 (Box 1237)
  - Small highly colored temples on East Wall, 1908; 15; 2369; 720; 5x7 (Box 1237)
  - Interior and front court of temple, detail of Temple of Urn, 1908; 16; 2370; 714; 5x7 (Box 1237)
  - Temple in East Wall, 1908; 17; 2371; 702; 5x7 (Box 1237)
  - Temple of the Urn in East Wall across gorge, 1908; 18; 2372; 698; 5x7 (Box 1237)
  - Rainbow temple, 1908; 19; 2373; 691; 5x7 (Box 1237)
  - Strata of rock in many colors, 1908; 20; 2374; 36; 5x7 (Box 1237)
  - Khazneh Firaun, 1908; 21; 2375; 696; 5x7 (Box 1237)
  - Khazneh Firaun from the Siq, 1908; 22; 2376; 588; 5x7 (Box 1237)
  - Entrance to the Siq, 1908; 23; 2377; 697; 5x7 (Box 1237)
  - The Siq from the Khazneh Firaun, 1908; 24; 2378; 729; 5x7 (Box 1237)